themefreesia.com 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy

**This Privacy Policy is issued to all our valued customers to the requirements of the Personal Data Protection.**

### Who we are

Our website address is: https://themefreesia.com.

### What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Forms

When you submit a support question we collect your first name, last name and your email address so that we can correspond with you.  
Your personal data will not only be stored in the website’s database. Also we use Mailchimp to send our newsletters and campaign

### Contact forms

When you submit via Contact Forms, nothing will be saved in our database. we collect your name, your email, your subject and your message via email.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

We use Google Analytics to track visitors on our website.  
Google Analytics uses cookies to collect this data.  
In order to be compliant with the new regulation Google included a [data processing amendment](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/dpa/dataprocessingamendment_20130906.html)The data we collect will be processed anonymously.We don’t use other Google services in combination with Google Analytics cookies. Data sharing is disabled

Theme Freesia is a web design/ development agency specializing in WordPress themes & plugins. We collect the information from every visitors to monitor traffic and fix the bugs.

### How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. 

### Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

### Your contact information

Theme Freesia  
171 reclamation street  
Hong Kong

### Additional information

If you have any queries or concern questions regarding this Privacy Policy then you may [Contact Us](https://themefreesia.com/contact-us) using below this information.

### How we protect your data

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. All the information collect during the transaction is secret. After a transaction, your private information will not be stored on our servers.

### What third parties we receive data from

We may include or offer or recommended any third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policy so we are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site nor the information. We also inquire to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Your Permission

By using our site, you give an affirmative reply to our privacy policy.

### Change Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policy then we will notify you by posting an announcement through emails or changes on this page. ThemeFreesia have right to amend the Privacy Policy if required.

### Third Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
